Guide to the Cornell University Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries' administrative records, 1961-2003.
Cornell University Olin, Kroch, Uris Libraries' administrative records, 1961-2003
- Series XVIII: Security and Safety
  - 32F. Fire Protection
    - 34.F.30 SBRA Feasibility Study-Olin (1992), 1992 (Box 15, Folder 47)
  - 34L. Life and Health Safety - General
    - 34.L Life & Health Safety--GEN. (Box 15, Folder 48)
    - 34.L.5 Building Inspections, 1990, 1993, 1995, 1998, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 49)
    - 34.L.10 Environmental Health & Safety--General, 1994-95, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 50)
    - 34.L.13 Equipment, 1979, 1991 (Box 15, Folder 51)
    - 34.L.15 Life Safety--Olin, 1983-87, 1994, 1997 (Box 15, Folder 52)
    - 34.L.20 Life Safety--Uris (Box 15, Folder 53)
  - 34P. Past Emergency Response
    - 34.P Past Emergency Resp. (Box 15, Folder 54)
    - 34.P.2 Emergency Phones--Olin (1993), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 55)
    - 34.P.4 Fire--Olin (1993), 1993 (Box 15, Folder 56)
    - 34.P.6 Power Failure (1994), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 57)
    - 34.P.8 Bomb Threat--Olin (1994), 1994 (Box 15, Folder 58)
  - 34S. Security - General
    - 34.S Security--General (Box 16, Folder 1)
    - 34.S.2 Closing Procedures, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 2)
    - 34.S.25 Slope Day, 1989-91, 1993-01 (Box 16, Folder 3)
    - 34.S.28 Thefts and Personal Security--CUL, 1997 (Box 16, Folder 4)
    - 34.S.30 Thefts and Personal Security --Olin, 1984-87, 1989-92, 1994-97, 2001 (Box 16, Folder 5)
    - 34.S.35 Thefts and Personal Security--Uris, 1996-97 (Box 16, Folder 6)
    - 34.S.40 3-M Security Gates, 1992, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 7)
    - 34.S.10 Security Committee--CUL, 1983, 1986, 1996 (Box 16, Folder 8)
    - 34.S.5 Loading Dock Cameras, 1995 (Box 16, Folder 9)
    - 34.S.15 Security--Olin--General, 1984, 1986, 1989-90, 1994, 1996-97 (Box 16, Folder 10)
    - 34.S.20 Security Policy--CUL, 1983, 1985 (Box 16, Folder 11)
- Series XIX: Statistics and General Data
  - 36A. Annual Statistical Reports
    - 36.A. Statistics (2000-01), 2000-01 (Box 17, Folder 42)
    - 36.A. Statistics (2001-02), 2001-02 (Box 17, Folder 43)
    - 36. Statistics & General Data (Box 16, Folder 12)
    - 36.A Annual Stat. Reports (Box 16, Folder 13)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91), 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 14)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92), 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 15)
    - 36.A.Statistics (1991-92)-Annex, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 16)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-AS, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 17)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-Collection Development, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 18)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-Echols, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 19)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-Annex, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 20)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-AS, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 21)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-Echols, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 22)
    - 36.A.Statistics (1990-91)-History of Science, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 23)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-Icelandic, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 24)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-ILL, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 25)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-M & A, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 26)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-MMN, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 27)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-Rare, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 28)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-Reference, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 29)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1990-91)-Wason, 1990-91 (Box 16, Folder 30)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-Icelandic, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 31)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-ILL, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 32)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-M & A, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 33)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-MMN, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 34)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-Rare Bks., 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 35)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-Reference, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 36)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-Wason, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 37)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1992-93)-Final, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 38)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1992-93)-Annex, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 39)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1993-94)-Olin/Kroch, 1993-94 (Box 16, Folder 40)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1992-93)-AS, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 41)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1992-93)-Asia, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 42)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1992-93)-Collection Development, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 43)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1992-93)-ILL, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 44)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1992-93)-MMN, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 45)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1992-93)-Rare, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 46)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1992-93)-Reference, 1992-93 (Box 16, Folder 47)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1993-94)-Forms, 1993-94 (Box 16, Folder 48)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1993-94)-Final, 1993-94 (Box 16, Folder 49)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1993-94)-ILS, 1993-94 (Box 16, Folder 50)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1993-94)-Uris, 1993-94 (Box 16, Folder 51)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1994-95)-Rep., 1994-95 (Box 16, Folder 52)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1994-95), 1994-95 (Box 16, Folder 53)
    - 36.A.Statistics (1995-96)-Olin/Kroch Uris, 1995-96 (Box 16, Folder 54)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1996-97), 1996-97 (Box 16, Folder 55)
    - 36.A Statistics (1997/98), 1997/98 (Box 16, Folder 56)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1998/99), 1998/99 (Box 16, Folder 57)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1999-00), 1999-00 (Box 16, Folder 58)
    - 36.A. Statistics (1991-92)-History of Science, 1991-92 (Box 16, Folder 20)
  - 36B. General Data - Cornell
    - 36.B.20 Enrollment, 1998-2001 (Box 10, Folder 9)
    - 36.B.40 Miscellaneous, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - 36C. General Data - CUL
    - 36.C.3 ARLE Metrics Project (2000/02), 2000 (Box 10, Folder 11)
    - 36.C.5 Basic Data, 1978-1997 (Box 10, Folder 12)
    - 36.C.10 Comparative Data, 1981-82, 1985-86, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 13)
    - 36.C.15 Cost Analysis, 1970-84 (Box 10, Folder 14)
    - 36.C.20 Technical Processing Data, 1998-2000 (Box 10, Folder 15)
    - 36.C.30 Users Survey (1990-91), 1990-91 (Box 10, Folder 16)
  - 36D. General Data - OKU
    - 36.D.10 Basic Data, 1995, 1998 (Box 10, Folder 17)
    - 36.D.20 Cataloging, 1989-98 (Box 10, Folder 18)
    - 36.D.25 Collections, 1995-96, 1999, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 19)
    - 36.D.45 Operations Data--General, 1993-94, 1996-98 (Box 10, Folder 20)
    - 36.D.50 Photocopy/Reader Reports (1993-96), 1993-96 (Box 10, Folder 21)
    - 36.D.50 Photocopy/Reader Reports (1996-99), 1996-99 (Box 10, Folder 22)
    - 36.D.50 Photocopy/Reader Reports (1999-02), 1999-02 (Box 10, Folder 23)
    - 36.D.60 RLIN Statistics, 1993-99 (Box 10, Folder 24)
    - 36.D.70 Uris Circulation Statistics, 1995-2000 (Box 10, Folder 25)
- Series XX: Technical Processing
  - 38A. Acquisitions - Contributions
    - 38.A.5 Approval Plans, 1987, 1990-91, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 26)
    - 38.A.10 Blanket Orders, 1979-84, 1986-88, 1990-91 (Box 10, Folder 27)
    - 38.A.15 Cancellation and Transfers, 1981-82, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 28)
    - 38.A.20 Monographic Series, 1980-82, 1984, 1987 (Box 10, Folder 29)
    - 38.A.25 Serials, 1979-82, 1988, 1991-92 (Box 10, Folder 30)
    - 38.A.30 Serials Check-In (1999), 1999 (Box 10, Folder 31)
  - 38C. Acquisitions - General
    - 38.C.10 Backlog, 1984-90, 1996-98 (Box 10, Folder 32)
    - 38.C.20 Claims, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 33)
    - 38.C.25 Gift Processing, 1994 (Box 10, Folder 34)
    - 38.C.30 Organization--Acquisitions Dept., 1987 (Box 10, Folder 35)
    - 38.C.40 Replacements, 1980-82, 1986, 1988 (Box 10, Folder 36)
    - 38.C.50 Technical Processing--Spec. Coll., 1989-90 (Box 10, Folder 37)
    - 38.C.60 Withdrawals/Transfer, 1994-95 (Box 10, Folder 38)
  - 38E. Cataloging - Asia Collections
    - 38.E.20 Location Codes, 1995 (Box 10, Folder 39)
    - 38.E.25 Media Collection Processing, 1998-99 (Box 10, Folder 40)
    - 38.E.30 Wason Cataloging--Outsourcing, 1997-98 (Box 10, Folder 41)
  - 38G. Cataloging - General
    - 38.G.5 Cataloging Priorities, 1994-96 (Box 10, Folder 42)
    - 38.G.20 Minimal Level Cataloging, 1984, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 43)
  - 38J. Recon Projects
    - 38.J.10 CJK Serials Recon (1995), 1994-96 (Box 10, Folder 44)
    - 38.J.30 OKU Recon, 1984, 1994-98, 2001 (Box 10, Folder 45)
  - 38L. Technical Services - General
    - 38.L.5 Backlog Reduction Planning (1994), 1994 (Box 10, Folder 46)
    - 38.L.6 Backlog Reduction Planning (1995-97), 1995-97 (Box 10, Folder 47)
    - 38.L.10 Organization, 1995-96, 2001-2002 (Box 10, Folder 48)
    - 38.L.20 Processing Priorities, 1981-83 (Box 10, Folder 49)
    - 38.L.25 Serials Check-In, 1999 (Box 10, Folder 50)
    - 38.L.30 Technical Services Group Minutes, 1987-91, 1995-96 (Box 10, Folder 51)
    - Africana--Administration (1999-2001), 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 44)
    - Africana-Administration (1997-1999), 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 45)
    - Africana--Collection Development, 1998-99 (Box 17, Folder 46)
    - Africana-Facilities, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 47)
    - Africana--Obichere Collection-Deed of Gift, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 48)
    - Africana--Obichere Collection--Contents, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 49)
    - Africana--Obichere Collection--General, 2000-2001 (Box 17, Folder 50)
    - Africana--Personnel, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 51)
    - Fine Arts--Administration, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 52)
    - Fine Arts-Collection Development, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 53)
    - Fine Arts--Facilities, 1997-2000 (Box 17, Folder 54)
    - Fine Arts--Personnel, 1998-2001 (Box 17, Folder 55)
    - Hotel--Administration, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 56)
    - Hotel--Collection Development (Box 17, Folder 57)
    - Hotel--Facilities (Box 17, Folder 58)
    - Hotel--Personnel, 1998, 2001 (Box 17, Folder 59)
    - ILR--Administration, 1999-2001 (Box 17, Folder 60)
    - ILR Administration (1997-1999), 1997-99 (Box 17, Folder 61)
    - ILR--Collection Development, 1996, 1998, 2000 (Box 17, Folder 62)
    - ILR--Personnel, 1998-99 (Box 17, Folder 63)
    - ILR--Facilities, 1998-99 (Box 17, Folder 64)
    - ILR--Strategic Planning, 1998-99 (Box 17, Folder 65)
    - Management--Administration, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 66)
    - Management--Collection Development, 2000-01 (Box 17, Folder 67)
    - Management--Facilities, 1997-98, 2000-01 (Box 17, Folder 68)
    - Management--Personnel, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 69)
    - Music--Administration, 1997-2001 (Box 17, Folder 70)
    - Music--Collection Development, 1997-99 (Box 17, Folder 71)
    - Music-Facilities, 1997, 1999 (Box 17, Folder 72)
    - Music--Personnel, 1997-1999 (Box 17, Folder 73)